Prophet T.B. Joshua sent his evangelists to minister the Morning Water
to the congregation in Jesus' name.
The name of Jesus is power and fire which makes satan and his agents flee.
As the Morning Water is ministered, every evil spirit in the lives of the people is exposed
and they are set free in the name of Jesus Christ.
Let's see what happens as the evangelist encounters this lady.
Now, speak! Fire! Who are you in this body?
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I told you before. I don't want to talk.
Say it again, in the name of Jesus Christ! Who are you in this body?
I have been here but I didn't talk.
When I came here, I didn't talk.
You have no choice than to speak.
I told you before. I'm her spiritual husband.
Apart from spiritual husband, who else is in this body? Speak, in the name of Jesus!
Speak out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Spirit of anger.
Now, as spirit of anger, what have you done to her?
I destroyed her.
How did you destroy her?
She is a good woman. You know that? She is a good woman.
I want to destroy her.
She likes helping people.
Look here!
As spirit of anger, what have you done to her? Answer my question!
I made her to have children with different men.
Now, she is pregnant.
How many men have you made her to have children for?
Three. Now, she is pregnant.
Tell us - as spirit of anger, what did you do to the first, second and third marriage?
I destroyed everything because she is my wife.
I married her.
I destroyed everything of hers because she is a good woman; she likes helping people.
"Ah, you have a problem. Please, take this money."
Why does she help people?
Why?
I want people to suffer.
Now, how did you destroy the second marriage?
She had married once; I destroyed it.
They followed her but I was there protecting her - nobody will marry her.
They came to marry her but she said, "No".
The three children she had - for how many men?
Speak, in the name of Jesus!
Three men.
She is pregnant; this is her third baby with a stupid man.
That man has his own problem.
As spirit of anger, what have you caused her marriage?
Speak, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I told you.
That what?
I destroyed the marriage because she is my wife.
How many times do I have to tell you that she is my wife?
When I came here, I never talked.
But you - you forced me to talk today.
I have been here three times. I never talked; I always hid myself.
Why do you make me to talk today? You!
Today is your day and Jesus wants you to speak.
You have no choice; you have to speak.
Now, speak! What else have you done to her?
I told you that she is a very good woman.
She has a nice future.
She likes God.
I made her to go to spiritualists.
Now, she knows God.
She says, "God of T.B. Joshua, please help me.
I have been coming there but I still have problems
but I will never give up with the God of T.B. Joshua. I will still go to Nigeria".
She has been coming here. She came here three times.
This woman is from where?
She is from which country? Speak out!
She is from Kenya. She got married in Japan.
Ok?
Ok. What have you done to her career?
It is a mistake to make me talk.
Come here! What have you done to her career?
Answer me, in the name of Jesus Christ!
What have you done to her career?
Which career - tell me? Which one? Do you see anything like career here?
I messed with her life since she was young, a small baby; I grew in her.
I have been there, doing these rubbish things.
She never even went to school.
She can speak English but she never went to school - she is trying!
She tried her best every day but I was still there.
But today, you make me to talk!
I was here a long time ago but I never talked.
What have you done to the father of the pregnancy?
That man is a married man.
I sent that man to make her pregnant.
That is my job.
Yes!
What is your gain, you demon?
She wanted to abort the baby.
The man said, "I will not send you for that abortion".
Because she is a Christian, she said, "I will have this baby; maybe it is a baby boy".
How did you enter her?
I entered her since she was born from her mother's womb.
I took her from that day.
She became my wife.
And who are you?
I'm her spiritual husband.
You have made the greatest mistake in allowing her to come here.
Now, you evil spirit that kills, steals and destroys -
today is an end of you and you have to leave her body right now, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Now, out of this body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I command Holy Ghost fire to consume and burn every negative spirit in your body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire all over your body!
From your head to the sole of your feet, in the name of Jesus!
You have no choice. You have to leave right now. Your time has expired.
Now, out of this body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I'm not going.
You have no choice. You have to leave in the name of Jesus Christ.
I will never leave her!
You have to leave!
You have to leave! You have no choice.
Now, pack all your things, you spirit of anger and all of you!
Now, out of this body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
You have no choice. You are making a mistake.
You have no choice. You have to leave, in the name of Jesus Christ.
You have to leave. Come here!
Come here!
You have to leave, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Now, you have to go!
You have to go! Continue to remove everything!
Everything that belongs to you - remove it right now, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Remember, you cannot deceive anyone! You have to come out!
That evil spirit, that demon that has been deposited in your body,
come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
I am a big snake.
I live here.
Now, all of you will leave right now!
All of you will leave!
You python, out of this body! Fire all over your body!
Fire all over your body!
Fire all over your body, in the name of Jesus Christ!
As a snake - can you move as a snake?
Move as a snake; let us see you!
Move as a snake, you demon!
When you move like this, what happens?
You know what happens.
She will not be happy.
Now all of you demons, in the name of Jesus Christ, in the blood of Jesus Christ,
out!
Your back on the floor, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus Christ, for her deliverance!
Thank You, Jesus Christ, for sending us this Morning Water
through your servant Prophet T.B. Joshua.
You are free, in Jesus' name.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Rise up, sister.
You are delivered through the medium of Morning Water
and you are delivered forever, in Jesus' name.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
I will never give up on You!
I have been suffering for long. Thank You!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Sister, your past is over.
Jesus Christ has just delivered you through the medium of the Morning Water
sent to you by Prophet T.B. Joshua and don't cry anymore.
Today, the Lord Jesus Christ has restored your joy
and you will continue to walk in the light of your testimony, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Bahati. I am originally from Kenya.
I live in Japan.
I am so happy to be here to testify about my deliverance.
My testimony goes like this.
I was born into a poverty-stricken family and did not know my father.
I grew up with my mum and she could not afford to send me to school.
When I was eight or nine years old, she passed away.
My sister took me when I was aged nine to help her in the house.
She introduced me to church; so, I started going to Sunday school.
By the grace of God, that church announced that there were people who would support
poor children who could not go to school.
By that time, I was nine years and I had never entered any school.
So, I agreed, wrote my name and was lucky to get the opportunity to go to school.
In school, because of my age, they could not take me to standard 1 or 2 but straight to class 4.
The people from class 4 knew how to read and write and speak English.
It was hard for me; I didn't know what to do in that class.
So what about you? Were you able to read, write and speak English?
No! I could not even say the alphabet.
It was so hard because those people could write very well.
I was so stressed and depressed.
Then, after one year, I went to the next class which was even harder.
Then, I went to another class - it was harder and harder.
So, when I went to class 7, it became like 'hell'. I could not cope any longer.
The depression was too much because you can even get a good job with reaching class 7.
I got tired.
I said to myself, "What kind of life is this!"
I met two women who introduced me to drinking.
I was drinking while going to school and the teacher noticed that I was drinking.
I stopped going to school because I could not catch anything.
I told my sister that I cannot continue going to school.
I started drinking.
Every day, I would drink and would come back home drunk.
My sister would beat me every day and get annoyed with me because I would be drunk.
I could not afford beer; so, I bought the cheap one that could kill people in Kenya.
At what age did you start taking alcohol?
I was maybe 15 years old.
Each time you took alcohol, what would happen to you?
I would fight and because it was very strong, I would drink quickly before the police came
and would blackout at anytime.
They would carry me and tell my sister,
"Your sister is in the garbage; she cannot walk".
So, people would carry me and bring me home and wash me without me knowing.
It continued like that. My sister got tired of me and I got tired of being beaten every day.
My sister told me, "You can move out and go and look for your own life. I'm tired!"
So, I went to those people who I used to drink with.
I met one man and told him, "Please, I don't have anywhere to go. Can I stay with you?"
So you mean that by this time, your elder sister had driven you out of the house
because she was tired of you?
Yes.
I started staying with the man as girlfriend and boyfriend.
I didn't know he was a gangster. I mean, an armed robber.
I knew it late but I didn't know where to go.
I stayed with him.
I said, "Anything can happen; I don't care because I don't know where to go".
One day, when we were living together, things became harder and harder
and he could not even afford to pay the rent.
So, the landlord told us, "Now, you can move out of my house
because you cannot pay the rent anymore".
So, we moved out and asked to stay with one of his friends who was also an armed robber
and he had two girlfriends.
After moving to his friend's house, they would go for three days and not come back.
We didn't have anything to eat for three days.
One day, he came back with the girlfriend.
Myself and another girlfriend were in the house for three days - no food!
So, they came and carried something but we didn't konw that it was money.
Afterwards, I told the one who I was always with in the house when they went out
that she should go and peep to see what her husband was doing with another woman.
So, she went and peeped through the door and told me, "Come here! They are counting money".
I responded, "Really?" She said, "Yes". I said that I would watch.
I watched and concluded that it was true - a lot of money.
We kept quiet and pretended that we didn't see any money.
Afterwards, they left, locked the door and left the money.
So, you mean that was part of the money they went and robbed?
Or stealing - I don't know. Yes.
They brought the money home?
Yes.
Ok.
I suggested to her, "Look, sister! We should break inside that house".
But we didn't know how to do it.
I told one man that I had lost my key and then he broke the lock of the door.
Then, we took the money and ran away.
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
So you mean that you and the other man's girlfriend carried all the money?
Yes, all the money.
We ran away to another town where nobody knew us.
We stayed there, went shopping, bought clothes, had our hair done,
bought shoes and became new people.
If you saw us, you would not recognise that we were the ones.
I went back to my sister and the lady went back to her village.
When I went back to my sister, she could not recognise me and asked, "Are you the one?"
I replied, "Yes, I'm your sister".
She told me, "Welcome back".
I told her how I managed to get the money.
I also gave her some money to buy me a small plot of land.
She told me to go to the city, that I should not stay there
because those people may look for me.
The police was also looking for those armed robbers.
Those armed robbers were looking for us.
Ok. You mean that police men were looking for them because of the robbery
and they were also looking for you because of their money you took away?
Yes.
So, tell us - how did you get into this life of prostitution after this?
After that, I went to Nairobi; my sister introduced me to a big international club.
In that club were foreigners and tourists from many countries.
I met a Japanese man from that club.
That time, I could not even speak English.
He asked me what he could help me with.
I asked the Japanese man to take me to where they have English classes.
He agreed to it and I started class.
After two months, the evil spirit came and chased the man away -
I took a knife and chased the Japanese man away.
That was how my English class ended.
I went back to prostitution - the same club.
I met another Japanese man who told me to stay at home,
that he would pay for everything I wanted and that he needed me to have a baby for him.
I didn't know he was married.
It was after I became pregnant that I discovered he was a married man.
After getting the baby, somebody called him that he was not supposed to work in Nairobi anymore,
that he had to go back to Japan.
He left me like that - no more contact.
I went back to prostitution and met another Japanese man.
So how many Japanese men were this now?
Three Japanese men.
The third one now?
Yes.
Ok. Then what happened?
That Japanese man was a divorcee but was ready to marry me.
He told me that he accepted me with my first baby.
We stayed in Kenya for two years and then we went to Japan.
After five or six years, I started beating him.
In his own country?
Yes.
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
So what happened when you started beating him?
After a while, I thought to myself that one day, I would kill this man
and then I will be taken to jail, that led me to divorce him.
So, I went through the process of divorce.
After coming back, I told him to sign but he refused.
Then, I took a knife and told him, "If you don't sign, I'm going to kill you".
So, he signed the divorce paper
and I looked for two men from Japan and slept with these men to sign for me too.
That was how I divorced my husband and the government took me.
Where the government took me to, there was a limited time...
So by this time, you had a child with this man?
Yes, I had another child - with the husband I divorced.
So making how many children now?
Two.
With two Japanese men?
Yes.
Ok. Go ahead.
When the government took me, at that place, there was a limit;
so, I could not go out at night and come back in the morning or over-drink
because it was strict.
So, you mean that you were now put in a restricted area?
Yes.
The government was taking care of you people - you had no chance to go out,
drink and go to the clubhouse?
Yes.
I stayed there for one year. I was stressed because I could not go out.
One day, I got my own house and freedom.
That was when I started drinking every day, from morning to morning,
leaving my children alone.
So, you mean that by this time, your two children were living with you
and you could not take care of them?
Yes.
So, when you were going out to drink and go to the clubhouse to meet men,
who would you leave your children with?
I used to leave them alone.
In the house?
Yes.
When I would come in the morning, I would start crying, asking myself why
and what had happened in my life.
That was how I was suffering.
Bahati - Deliverance Testimony
Ok. So how old were these children then?
My eldest child is 13 and the other one is seven years old.
After getting my apartment, I met this Japanese lady.
She was married to an African man.
That woman said, "Ah, you have so much stress. Let me introduce you to idol worship".
I told her, "No, I cannot worship idols; I am a Christian".
She continued disturbing me for almost two years.
One day - because she was married to a black man - I decided to face the husband
to stop this woman from disturbing me.
So, I met with the husband.
He became my boyfriend and now, I am pregnant by him.
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
So you mean the African man you met where you are living?
Yes, my neighbour.
Who is married to a Japanese woman?
Yes, they are my neighbours.
So when you went to him because you didn't want to worship idols with the wife...
Yes, so I didn't know...
So you went to the husband for him to talk to the wife
so that she would stop disturbing you?
Yes.
And you became friends - boyfriend and girlfriend?
So the pregnancy you have now is for who?
It's for him.
So did the wife know about it?
I told the wife that I was pregnant by her husband.
And what did she say?
She asked me what I was going to do and if I would have an abortion or what.
I said, "No", that I was a Christian and would not have an abortion
but that I didn't need anything from her - God would provide for the baby.
She complained that the husband was down and that the money was not coming in like before.
So, the two children you had with those two Japanese men - where are they now?
They are in Japan.
Tell us how you came to know about The SCOAN.
There is a Kenyan woman who lives in Japan.
She introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
Then I started watching and saw people with similar problems to mine.
I continued watching.
Last week, I got my complete deliverance, in Jesus' name.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus!
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
A while ago, we watched the deliverance and heard all that the demon said.
Can you tell us - what was your experience at that point in time
when the Morning Water was ministered to you? What were the things you saw?
That time, the anger was much.
If I had caught the evangelist at that time,
maybe, I could have killed her because I was so angry but it was not me.
I didn't know what made me so angry and so powerful.
So all this while, you didn't know that all the life you were living,
it was as a result of these demons - the spiritual husband and the snake?
I didn't know until I started watching Emmanuel TV and witnessed people's testimonies.
Then, I saw similar problems to mine.
I said to myself, "Yes, I think I have the same problem as this woman".
I trust and love God and said that I would never let Him go.
What was in that Morning Water that was ministered to you
that would make you lose your temper - you felt like fighting and destroying?
I don't know. It was the spirit within me.
My character changed and I became violent.
Ok. Since after your deliverance, can you tell us of the changes you have noticed in your life.
I feel light in my body.
My stomach used to feel heavy as if I were carrying many babies.
I could not sleep on my left side but now, I can - even for two hours.
I also used to eat a lot.
Do you still have the urge to go out to the clubhouse and meet men?
You have been here for the whole week.
Do you still have the urge to go out and meet men?
No, I am totally delivered.
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
Glory be to God!
We thank God Almighty for your life and now that you are delivered,
what is your word of advice to people that are listening to you all over the world
and people who are still living the kind of life you lived in the past?
What advice do you have for them?
My advice to the whole world is to never give up on God.
Come close to Him.
He will deliver you the way He delivered me and your past shall be over.
Amen.
Don't struggle outside.
Hallelujah! Let us clap for Jesus Christ!
Indeed, it is only by deliverance that our past can be over.
So, remember, the former life you were living was a life out there in the world.
It is now that you are delivered - now you are Christian,
now you are a born-again, now you are a believer.
I want to encourage you to make the Word of God the standard for your life
and embrace the wonderful Word of God as the most effective instrument for change.
Through this deliverance, your life will be restored and you will come back some day
to give a wonderful testimony of breakthrough and blessing in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Bahati
Deliverance Testimony
RV: Mel Flowers 27/03/2019